[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What are the 4 main components of an Android application?",
    "correctAnswer": "Activity, Service, Content Provider, Broadcast Receiver",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fragment, Intent Service, Content Loader, Receiver",
      "Manifest, Gradle Scripts, Res Folder, Java Folder",
      "WorkManager, Room, Coroutines, Navigation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is Context?",
    "correctAnswer": "The current state of the application",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Understand how the user interacts with our app",
      "The location in memory of the app on the device",
      "Where the user is interacting in our app"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is Context used for?",
    "correctAnswer": "Get information regarding the activity and application",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Understand how the user interacts with our app",
      "The location in memory of the app on the device",
      "Relates to the .xml files"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is an Activity",
    "correctAnswer": "A single screen that the user can interact with",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Handles long running operation without user interaction",
      "Allows the application to response to Android intents",
      "Manages access to a central repository of data"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is a Service",
    "correctAnswer": "Handles long running operation without user interaction",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A single screen that the user can interact with",
      "Allows the application to response to Android intents",
      "Manages access to a central repository of data"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is a Broadcast Receiver",
    "correctAnswer": "Allows the application to response to Android intents",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A single screen that the user can interact with",
      "Handles long running operation without user interaction",
      "Manages access to a central repository of data"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is a Content Provider",
    "correctAnswer": "Manages access to a central repository of data",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A single screen that the user can interact with",
      "Handles long running operation without user interaction",
      "Allows the application to response to Android intents"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the lifecycle of an Activity?",
    "correctAnswer": "onCreate, onStart, onResume, onPause, onStop, onDestroy",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "onAttach, onCreateView, onViewCreated, onDestroy, onDetach",
      "startService, bindService, unbindService, stopService",
      "startActivity, onContinue, onBreak, endActivity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the use of Bundle?",
    "correctAnswer": "Used to pass data between Activities or Fragments",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Serializes our custom objects",
      "To group our android components",
      "Wraps our intents"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is AIDL?",
    "correctAnswer": "Android Interface Definition Language",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "All In Defined Logs",
      "Also Interactable Don't Lie",
      "Android Interaction Design Lingo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What data types are supported by AIDL?",
    "correctAnswer": "String, List, Map, CharSequence and Java primitives",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Only Java primitives",
      "Custom types defined in the manifest",
      "Android specific types"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What is the Android Manifest?",
    "correctAnswer": "Information about the application Android needs to know about",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Where our Java/Kotlin code is written",
      "Information about our min/target SDK",
      "Android specific types"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What is an intent",
    "correctAnswer": "A messaging object used to request an action from other components",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "An object only used to start other activities",
      "Information about the application the Android needs to know about",
      "Handles long running operation without user interaction"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Explicit Intents are used for...",
    "correctAnswer": "Invoking an android component",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Invoking various system components based on type",
      "Getting information regarding the activity",
      "A hard coded message for other applications"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Implicit Intents are used for...",
    "correctAnswer": "Invoking various system components based on type",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Invoking an android component",
      "Getting information regarding the activity",
      "A hard coded message for other applications"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What is an ANR?",
    "correctAnswer": "Application Not Responding",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "App Not Ready",
      "Application No Retry",
      "Always Never Run"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "An ANR can be caused by...",
    "correctAnswer": "No response to an input event after 5 seconds",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "Android not recognizing your app",
      "Your Kotlin code not matching Java code",
      "Components not being specified in the manifest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What are the activity launch modes?",
    "correctAnswer": "standard, singleTop, singleTask, singleInstance",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "default, singleton, module, viewModel",
      "onCreate, onStart, onResume, onPause, onStop, onDestroy",
      "FrameLayout, ConstraintLayout, LinearLayout, RelativeLayout"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What is the compileSDK?",
    "correctAnswer": "The version of API the application is compiled against",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "The API level of the Android device where the app expects to run",
      "The minimum API level where the application is able to run",
      "Tells the compiler which code language to use"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What is the targetSDK?",
    "correctAnswer": "The API level of the Android device where the app expects to run",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "The version of API the application is compiled against",
      "The minimum API level where the application is able to run",
      "Tells the SDK which device type it should target"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What is the minSDK?",
    "correctAnswer": "The minimum API level where the application is able to run",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "The version of API the application is compiled against",
      "The API level of the Android device where the app expects to run",
      "Tells the SDK how much code is needed to begin the application"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What does ProGuard do for our app?",
    "correctAnswer": "Shrinks, obfuscates and optimizes our code",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "Bundles our generated classes",
      "The system that sends notifies us about warnings and errors in our IDE",
      "We do not have ProGuard in Android"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What is not an example of a normal permission?",
    "correctAnswer": "SEND_SMS",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "INTERNET",
      "SET_ALARM",
      "BLUETOOTH"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What is not an example of a dangerous permission?",
    "correctAnswer": "ACCESS_NOTIFICATION_POLICY",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "RECORD_AUDIO",
      "SEND_SMS",
      "ACCESS_FINE_LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What is a dangerous permission?",
    "correctAnswer": "A permission that can affect the user's privacy",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "A permission that can crash the app is not handled",
      "A permission that leaves the app vulnerable to being hacked",
      "A permission that can overheat the device"
    ]
  }
]

